[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad?
Billy? Sweetie?
Dad…
Are you leaving?
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hello? What's taking you
so long to respond?
So, can I see you tomorrow?
Brandon, I'm sorry.
I'm not available.
You always say that.
You're just making up
excuses at this point.
What? Have you changed your mind about me?
- Ma'am, it's done. Everything's installed.
- All done?
Okay, let me check it.
Okay. It's working now, sir.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Auntie Pres?
- Yes?
- The CCTV cameras are done.
- Oh, okay.
Billy, I have something to give you.
- One for you, one for me.
- Mm-hmm.
There you go.
This is how you use it.
- Remove this side.
- Mm-hmm.
- Aim at their eyes.
- Yes.
- Press it. Aim towards the bad guy.
- Copy.
I know how to use it, Auntie. Thank you.
- Okay. Here.
- Sorry for making you worried.
[POLICE OFFICER]
You can count on us. Don't worry.
We will do our best.
You know, that's what you guys always say.
But nothing ever happens.
I'll tell the truth.
That Caloy guy…
He courted me before.
But I turned him down.
I mean, it's like he's obsessed with me.
I kept rejecting him,
but he remained persistent.
Are you saying that
you have nothing to do with this?
Here.
What's this? Where is this?
I have no idea.
I had nothing to do with it.
Billy Cariño's house.
Billy's house?
We won't have any peace
until that Billy leaves us alone!
Look, if you want--
Uh, Ma…
What I want
is for you to let me deal with Billy.
I'll handle her, okay?
I can do that.
[SIGHS]
[SLAMS PALM DOWN]
[SIGHS AGAIN]
[SIGHS]
Something to cool your head.
Thanks.
Mmm.
[WRAPPER RUSTLING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Thanks.
- I needed that.
- I know, right?
I'm sorry, dude.
I get it.
It's okay.
I just don't want you to experience
what happened with my mom.
It's been years.
It's still a cold case.
They still haven't caught
the hit-and-run driver who hit her.
That's why I want Caloy to be caught.
And for Bea to be held accountable.
They have to pay for what they did.
Before they do anything else.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Excuse me.
He's here.
Okay. Thank you, Val.
- [SIGHS]
- [BILLY WHISPERS] Okay.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
I'm here.
Sorry, sir. Just a moment.
[PRECIOUS] Gosh…
Didn't I tell you yesterday
that I wasn't available?
Why did you still come?
Don't get mad at me
when I already told you I couldn't go.
Why can't you just leave
Oliver to himself?
He's not a baby.
You just don't understand.
Understand what?
- That you're just leading me on?
- It's not like that, Brandon.
You know, you just wasted my time.
That's not true!
If it's not true, let's go.
- Come with me. Let's go.
- Brandon, that hurts!
Bro.
Don't force her to come
if she doesn't want to.
You should go.
I'll call security if you don't.
Brandon, please just leave.
Go on.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
I also have a background in marketing,
sales, and computer programming.
I am certain, ma'am, that I am qualified
for the executive assistant position.
Hmm… Okay.
We'll consider your application
and call you.
You may go ahead. Thank you for your time.
All right.
Thank you.
[TALIA] And so, Em, I need an update
on that jewelry designer.
- The one that I requested some time ago.
- Yes, ma'am. Okay.
- It's really important.
- [BEA SQUEALS]
- Hi, Ms. Talia!
- [TALIA] Ah…
Uh… and you are?
- Bea. Bea Mercado!
- Oh! [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Hello!
Good afternoon, Madam Talia!
She's an applicant,
and she's about to leave.
- I'm so sorry.
- You're so beautiful.
- You're my idol! Your skin is glowing!
- This way, miss.
- [TALIA] Okay.
- Let's go.
Okay. Whatever.
- [WOMAN] Go home.
- I really need that update.
- Okay, Em?
- [BEA] Thank you.
[TALIA] Make sure it's already prepared.
I need to know it.
[RESOLUTE MUSIC PLAYING]
[RESOLUTE MUSIC FADES]
Everyone, let us welcome
the newest member of the LoveList family,
Mr. Morrie Velasco.
[EVERYONE]
Welcome!
And Charm, like we talked about,
Morrie will be joining our marketing team.
- Yes, welcome, Morrie!
- Thank you, Ms. Charm.
I'm so honored. I'll finally get to work
with the award-winning team
behind the phenomenal
Happily Ever After!
[BLAIRE] Oh, that's nothing!
Speaking of awards…
Let's congratulate our chief!
She'll receive
the Young Entrepreneur of the Year Award
from no less than
The Philippine Business Society!
[APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
Thank you. That's an award for all of us.
So, congratulations, everyone.
Take note,
the event is at Manila Royale Suites.
And there's even a free hotel stay
for the awardees!
[STAFF EXCLAIM HAPPILY]
Chief, all of us are included, right?
Absolutely! Let's go.
[CHARM] OMG! What are we going to wear?
- Let me borrow your clothes!
- Sure!
[TONI] Will they fit her?
I'm sure Ms. Camille is fuming.
You got an award, and she didn't.
Because she trusted the wrong person,
choosing Bea.
Let's move on from that, Morrie.
The important thing is that she
has no connection to Pebblng,
or here in LoveList.
So as far as this turf is concerned,
we have nothing to worry about.
But, chief…
What about the home turf?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
It's all good.
Yes, don't worry about it.
Thank you, Toni.
Okay.
Anyway, are you ready?
Mm-hmm. Yes.
Charm, take care of Morrie.
What will we wear?
- [TONI] What should we wear?
- We should go home.
[PRECIOUS] LoveList is finally
back on its feet.
Just focus on getting better.
You're not thinking of
getting back at them, are you?
But they've gone too far, Auntie Pres.
But this will never end.
If you retaliate,
they'll just retaliate again.
Think of your brother.
That's exactly why I'm worried, Auntie.
They were able to break into our house.
What's next?
I need to stop them
before Oliver gets hurt.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR HONKING IN DISTANCE]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CALOY] Hey!
Caloy?!
Well?
What do you think?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[BOTTLE THUDS]
Boss.
I think you've had too much to drink.
You know,
I was young…
when I lost my mom.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
And Grandpa…
With his condition,
I feel like I'm losing him too.
And now Billy.
[SIGHS] I nearly lost her.
But she's safe, isn't she?
But what if she hadn't been?
Nothing will happen.
Right?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I just realized
how important she is to me.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] I knew it.
She's like my family.
Her, Oliver, and Auntie Pres.
Ever since we were in high school,
whenever Grandpa had a gig,
he'd leave me at Billy's house.
Dude, you're eating three pieces?!
Save some for the rest of us!
This came from my grandpa, right?
Fine. Have as much as you want.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- I don't like that.
- Oh yeah!
You like the drumsticks.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Peace.
- Fine. We're good now.
- [PLATES CLATTERING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SINGING] ♪ Oh, light ♪
♪ In the cold night ♪
Cut!
Cut, cut. Okay?
Okay.
[YOUNG BILLY] This is a serenade!
You're singing like you're in a funeral.
How could we win like that?
- Again.
- Okay.
- Do it properly.
[CLEARS THROAT] Go.
[SINGING] ♪ Oh, light ♪
♪ In the cold night ♪
♪ You're like a star in the sky ♪
Oh, my dear.
I hope I can hear you
finally say yes to me.
Yes, my dear.
I also love you!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[IN UNISON] That's it!
We're so good! We got it!
[GIGGLING]
- Okay, let's do it again.
- Okay.
We'll definitely win! Okay!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Wake up!
- What?
Look, you're sleeping again!
Mm!
You jerk!
- [YOUNG JORDAN GRUNTS]
- [YOUNG BILLY LAUGHS]
[GIGGLING]
[YOUNG BILLY] You jerk!
- [YOUNG BILLY GRUNTS]
- [YOUNG JORDAN LAUGHING]
Just go write there,
or you're going to fail.
I'll tell on you to your teacher!
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[YOUNG JORDAN] Dude!
What?
[YOUNG JORDAN] Here!
- I got 85 percent!
- [YOUNG BILLY CHUCKLES]
Look, I got 85!
- I passed!
- [YOUNG BILLY CHUCKLES]
Here!
Okay, fine. Congrats.
[YOUNG BILLY] But it has to be like this!
I got 100 percent.
[TEASING PREENING NOISE]
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
- You're the best.
- I really am!
Next quarter, we must both
score a hundred percent.
You should just avoid sleeping.
You always sleep in class!
- Let's go inside.
- Close the gate!
Last one in is a rotten egg!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
We both lost our mothers.
We were both broken.
But Billy…
She used her pain
to rise up.
She's so strong.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
She always told me,
"Don't give up. Keep going. Go, go, go!"
When it comes to me composing my songs,
it's also because of her.
You even made a new song, right?
That love song.
[CHUCKLES]
- Friendship song.
- Friendship song?
- He said it's about friendship.
- Friendship song.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
WHERE'S OUR DESTINATION?
YOU ARE THE CAPTAIN
I'LL RIDE YOUR WAVE WHEREVER IT TAKES ME
DO YOU KNOW? WHEN I FOUND YOU
EVERYTHING CHANGED
WHEREVER I GO, MY HEART WON'T BE LOST
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA] You…
Why did you come here?
Someone might recognize you.
You know it's dangerous.
[CHUCKLES] Even you didn't recognize me.
Right?
I'm pretty good, aren't I?
[CALOY CHUCKLES] I'm really good.
You--
You don't have to worry.
I checked the surroundings.
No one was watching you.
Just me.
I was the only one.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA EXHALES DEEPLY]
'Bi…
Are you okay?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[SNIFFLES AGAIN]
[SIGHS]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Caloy, I don't understand.
I've done everything I can
to give my mother a good life.
[BEA SNIFFLES]
What's happening?
I'm back to square one.
I want Billy's life
because it should've been mine.
That should've been mine,
but Billy just had to steal it!
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
I've heard so many love stories.
But do you know whose love story
I'm most excited about?
Yours.
But maybe I don't really
have a love story.
Sometimes, the best closure
is no closure at all.
There's nothing I can do about it, right?
Just use me.
I'll help you.
[JORDAN] Bea's mom's name
is Mariela Mercado.
Her mother has
a history of mental illness.
That's serious, Jordan.
Maybe she really needs professional help.
[BILLY] A woman has been
standing outside for a while now.
I can't make her out clearly.
- I'll check it out.
- No, you won't!
Ma?
[MARIELA] I can't bear to
see you suffer, my dear.
Okay. Please hurry up.
Thank you.
Why did you call the police?
I didn't come here to make a scene.
Billy, have mercy on me and my daughter.